所以  系统是如何知道地图软件能够处理某个Intent的呢
So, how did the system know that the Maps
地图软件的每个Activity
app could handle this Intent? The activity within the
都会包含这样一个Intent过滤器
Maps app included an intent filter like this one
在它的manifest里  它指明了
within its manifest entry. It indicates that the Maps
地图软件能够执行这个view action
app is capable of performing this view action on
在scheme为geo的所有数据上  你可以
all data which has a geo scheme. You can
使用Intent过滤器为你的Activity定义一个
use intent filters for your activities to define the
它能胜任的行为 可选择地 还可以定义
actions they're capable of performing, and optionally, the kind
它能处理的数据类型
of data that they can perform it on. So,
当你使用一个implicit intent去
when you use an implicit intent to address or
请求启动一个Activity  很像你对
request to start an activity, much like you did
Catherine以及openweathermap.org链接做的一样，Android会解析这类请求
with Catherine and the openweathermap.org link, Android resolves this request
通过检查每个安装在该设备上的Activity的Intent过滤器
by checking the intent filters of every activity that's
直到系统找到可能的最佳
installed on the device until it finds the best possible
匹配  如果有多种匹配方式  就根据网址域名的实际情形
match. If multiple activities match, as in the case
使用者有选择的机会
with the web url, the user is given a choice.